Guide to the Rice University Margarett Root Brown College Records, 1965-2014 UA 074
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series X: Photographs, 1965-2010; 174596
  - Student Life, 1972, 1974-1975, 2010, n.d.; 174618 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Series XI: Audio/Visual, 1988-2009; 174597
  - Beer Bike (2 8mm tapes), 1987, 1988; 148161 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Dr. Franz Brotzen speaking about the history of Brown College and the college system (2 DVDs and mini-DV), February 27, 2008; 35689 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Spring College Night (2 8mm tapes), 1987, 1988; 172974 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Theater (8mm tape and 3 DVDs), 2007; 172971 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    General
    Includes the following videos: A Match Made in Heaven, A Midsummer Night's Dream, Jesus Christ Superstar, and Guys and Dolls
  - Track Meet, unknown (2 8mm tapes), 1987, n.d.; 172969 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Series XII: Memorabilia, 2002-2012; 174598
  - Men of Brown Calendar, 2011; 159284 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Beer Bike Koozie, 2012; 174619 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Frosted shot glass with college crest (2), n.d.; 174620 (Box 18)
  - Glass with college crest, n.d.; 174621 (Box 18)
  - Class of 2002 graduation-themed owl in Brown College jersey, 174622 (Box 18)
  - Tea cup and saucer with college crest, 174623 (Box 18)
  - Brown/RPC sunglasses, n.d.; 174624 (Box 19)
  - Associate's Night decorations (2), March 2011; 174625 (Box 19)
  - Bandana with college crest, 174626 (Box 19)
  - Bacchanalia T-Shirt, 2008; 184650 (Box 19)
  - Guys and Dolls T-Shirt, 2009; 172980 (Box 19)
  - Bacchanalia T-Shirt, 2011; 184651 (Box 19)
  - Beer Bike T-Shirt (2), 2011; 174627 (Box 19)
  - O-Week, 2011; 184652 (Box 19)
  - Bacchanalia T-Shirt (2), 2012; 174628 (Box 19)
  - Beer Bike T-Shirt (3), 2012; 174629 (Box 19)
  - O-Week T-Shirt, 2012; 184653 (Box 19)
  - Beer Bike T-Shirt, 2013; 184654 (Box 19)
  - O-Week T-Shirt, 2013; 184655 (Box 19)
  - College T-Shirt, n.d.; 184656 (Box 19)
  - College T-Shirt, n.d.; 184657 (Box 19)
  - Individualized sports T-Shirt, 174630 (Box 19)
  - Bacchanalia cloth sign, 2011; 174631 (Box 19)
- Series XIII: Google Drive Digital Archive, 184658
  The following items, organized by former president John Muller, comprise the digital archive for Brown College as of July 2014. These items were downloaded from the Brown College Digital Archive Google Drive, converted to pdf files, saved to an internal server, and printed. The digital files will be kept until June 2016. After that, the digital files will be deleted, but the physical files will remain in the collection.
  - Subseries A: Joey Spinella, 2011-2012, 184659
    - Executive Council, 184660 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Committees, 184661 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Subseries B: Ivan Huang, 2012-2013, 184662
    - Accountability Meeting Minutes, 184663 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Cabinet Agendas, 184664 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Cabinet Minutes, 184665 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Committees, 184666 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Executive Cabinet Meeting Agendas, 184667 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Executive Cabinet Meeting Minutes, 184668 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Floor Rep Meeting Minutes, 184669 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Housing and Room Assignments, 184670 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Budget, 184671 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Executive Cabinet, 184672 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Subseries C: John Muller, 2013-2014, 184673
    - 50th Anniversary Committee, 184674 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Cabinet Agendas, 184675 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Cabinet Minutes, 184676 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Executive Cabinet Agendas, 184677 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Executive Cabinet Minutes, 184678 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Executive Cabinet Retreats, 184679 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Subseries D: Changeover, 2014, 184680
    - Committees, 184681 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Internal Vice President, 184682 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - President, 184683 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Secretary, 184685 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Student Association Senator, 184686 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Treasurer, 184684 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Series XIV: Scrapbooks, 184692
  To preserve the photographs inside, some of these scrapbooks, especially those that had a lot of descriptive information but harmful enclosures, were disassembled. Scans were made of the scrapbooks and were placed within their respective folders.
  - 1965, 184694 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 1976/1977 (1 of 2), 184695 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - 1976/1977 (2 of 2), 184696 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - 1977/1978 (1 of 3), 184697 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - 1977/1978 (2 of 3), 184698 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - 1977/1978 (3 of 3), 184699 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 1981/1982 (1 of 2), 184700 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - 1981/1982 (2 of 2), 184701 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Photo Album, 1983/1984; 184702 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - 1984/1985, 184703 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - 1985/1986 (1 of 3), 184704 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - 1985/1986 (2 of 3), 184705 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 1985/1986 (3 of 3), 184706 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - 1986/1987, 184707 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Photo Album, 1987/1988; 184708 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - O-Week Photo Album, 1990; 184709 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - 1990/1991 (1 of 2), 184710 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 1990/1991 (2 of 2), 184711 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - 1991/1992 (1 of 2), 184712 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 1991/1992 (2 of 2), 184713 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Photo Album, 1992/1993; 184714 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - 1993/1994, 184715 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - 1998/1999, 184716 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Loose Photographs and Memorabilia, 1970s-2000s; 184717 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - 1972/1973, 184718 (Box 26)
  - 1973/1974, 184719 (Box 26)
  - 1994/1995, 184720 (Box 27)
  - 1997/1998, 184721 (Box 27)
  - 1999/2000, 184722 (Box 28)
  - 2002/2003, 184723 (Box 28)
- Series XV: Slides and Photographs
  Unless otherwise noted, all folders contain slides.
  - 1969/1970 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - 1972/1973 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - 1973/1974 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - 1974/1975 (Box 29, Folder 5-6)
  - 1975/1976 (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
  - 1976/1977 (Box 30, Folder 3-4)
  - 1977/1978 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - 1977/1978 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - 1978/1979 (Box 31, Folder 2-3)
  - 1979/1980 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - 1979/1980 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - 1980/1981 (Box 32, Folder 2-3)
  - 1981/1982 (Box 32, Folder 4-5)
  - 1982/1983 (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
  - 1983/1984 (photographs) (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - 1984/1985 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - 1985/1986 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - 1987/1988 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - 1980s (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Series XVI: Google Drive Digital Archive
  These items were downloaded from the Brown College Digital Archive Google Drive, converted to pdf files, saved to an internal server, and printed. The digital files will be kept until June 2017. After that, the digital files will be deleted, but the physical files will remain in the collection.
  - Subseries A: Joey Spinella, 2011-2012
    - President Joey Spinella files
  - Subseries B: Ivan Huang, 2012-2013
    - President Ivan Huang files
  - Subseries C: John Muller, 2013-2014
    - President John Muller files
    - 2014 changeover files
  - Subseries D: Reilly Solis, 2014-2015
    - President Reilly Solis files
  - Subseries E: Tom Carroll, 2015-2016
    - President Tom Carroll files
  - Cabinet Agendas, 2014/2015 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Cabinet Minutes, 2014/2015 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Committees, 2014/2015 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Constitution, 2014/2015 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - EC Agendas, 2014/2015 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - EC Minutes, 2014/2015 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - EC Spring Retreat, 2014/2015 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Elections, 2014/2015 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Floor Rep Meetings, 2014/2015 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Initiative Fund Request, 2014/2015 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Senate Minutes, 2014/2015 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Series XVII: Student Life
  - Activities, 2005-2006 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Activities, 2006-2007 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Series XVIII: Memorabilia
  - Beer Bike T-shirts, 1999, 2001, 2002 (Box 35)
  - O-Week T-shirts, 1998, 2000 (Box 35)
  - Powderpuff Championship T-shirt, 2000 (Box 35)
  - Graduation stole, n.d. (Box 35)
  - Small brass decorative item with crest, n.d. (Box 35)
- Series XIV: Addendum
  - Brown College Group Photo (Map-drawer 147, Item 6)
  - Brown College Group Photo, 1986-1987 (Map-drawer 147, Item 7)
  - Brown College Group Photo, 1988-1989 (Map-drawer 147, Item 8)
  - Brown College Group Photo, 1987-1988 (Map-drawer 147, Item 9)
  - Brown College Group Photo, Spring 1995 (Map-drawer 147, Item 10)
  - Brown College Group Photo, Spring 2004 (Map-drawer 147, Item 11)
  - Brown College Group Photo, Spring 1991 (Map-drawer 147, Item 12)
  - Brown College Group Photo, 1998 (Map-drawer 147, Item 13)
  - Brown College Group Photo, 2011-04 (Map-drawer 156, Item 3)
  - Brown College Group Photo, 1993 (Map-drawer 156, Item 4)
  - Brown College Group Photo, Spring 2007 (Map-drawer 156, Item 5)
  - Brown College Group Photo, Spring 1992 (Map-drawer 156, Item 6)
  - Brown College Group Photo, Spring 2003 (Map-drawer 156, Item 7)
  - Brown College Group Photo, Spring 2006 (Map-drawer 156, Item 8)
  - Brown College Group Photo, Spring, 1999 (Map-drawer 156, Item 9)
  - Brown College Group Photo, Spring 2005 (Map-drawer 156, Item 10)
  - Brown College Group Photo, Spring 2000 (Map-drawer 156, Item 11)
  - Brown College Group Photo, Spring 2008 (Map-drawer 156, Item 12)
  - Brown College Group Photo, 1997-03 (Map-drawer 156, Item 13)
  - Brown College Group Photo, Spring 1994 (Map-drawer 170, Item 2)
  - Brown College Group Photo, Spring 2009 (Map-drawer 170, Item 3)
  - Brown College Group Photo, Spring 1996 (Map-drawer 170, Item 4)
  - Brown College Group Photo, Spring 2001 (Map-drawer 170, Item 5)
  - Brown College Group Photo, Spring 2002 (Map-drawer 170, Item 6)